Richard Pryor: Live on the Sunset Strip is a comedy,
documentary film directed by Joe Layton.
Richard Pryor's stand-up act includes his frank discussion about his freebasing
addiction, as well as the infamous night on June 9, 1980 that he caught on fire.
Self, played by Richard Pryor.
Stoned Hippie (uncredited), played by Gene Cross.
Self - Audience Member (uncredited), played by Julie Hampton.
Self - Audience Member (uncredited), played by Jesse Jackson.
Richard Pryor: Live on the Sunset Strip is the seventeenth
album by American comedian Richard Pryor.
Produced by Pryor and Biff Dawes, the album was released
alongside the comedian's film of the same name in 1982.
The material includes Pryor's frank discussion of his drug addiction and of the
night that he caught on fire while freebasing cocaine in 1980.
The album later won the Grammy Award for Best Comedy Recording in 1982.
The tone is lighthearted.